[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 6, "question": "Mom, you're not wearing my clothes, are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 7, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "Did you see a little you sprouting here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "RB", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "Her personality, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "They said, well, whatever you see on TV with Sharon and Kelly and the others, underpinning it all, underpinning all the kind of caricature stuff that you have on the telly, actually you're very dedicated, determined family people, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", ",", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "RB", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "VBN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sharon", "Kelly"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "Is it particularly important in somewhere like America and Hollywood in particular to be tough?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "God, you have to be.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "Superstar?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "That wasn't the restaurant that Sean Penn and Scarlet Johansson were in, was it, by any chance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "You're such an ass.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sean Penn", "Scarlet Johansson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "Was it that loud?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "It was that loud.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "Now talking of fighting losing battles, have either of you been invited to the royal wedding?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "Get out of here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "All Brits want to go to the royal wedding, don't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNPS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "Wouldn't you like to go?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "Yes, but have you met the Prince William?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["William"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ":", "DT", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "What did you think of him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "He's a lovely young -- a lovely, lovely young guy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "Have I been out with him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "No?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "Is it a particular pressure that only the kids of very famous people understand?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "That's a completely different level I can't even compare myself on because I don't have an entire country looking at me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "For her who just come in to this family, just like Diana, huge pressure, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "Amazing to have, you know, from now on her life will never be the same again ever in good and bad.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Diana"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "You know Fergie well, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Fergie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "``", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "Didn't you and Fergie do a weird thing in a restroom -- in a London restaurant one night?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "To (INAUDIBLE).", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Fergie"], "LOCATION": ["London"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "Did you go down and pretend to be restroom attendants?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "Yes, we were showing people into the ladies room.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "It's just -- I hope Kate Middleton can deal with it because it's going to be a phenomenal thing for her to have to try and cope with, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "NN", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "I have a question.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kate Middleton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "Why are we talking about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "Are you going to the wedding?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "You support them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "Because my mom has cancer and I'm clearly on drugs and it's horrible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "And you were on drugs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "For sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "You know what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "She's thinking, going, I was so skinny.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "But it would have been easy for them not to have dealt with all that crap that came into their lives without exposure of national television?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "Was it Kelly that stepped up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "VBD", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kelly"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Is that when you two really bonded, do you think, in that period?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "CD", "RB", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "No, we were already close.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "Are you trying to make me cry?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "NN", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Did you ever think you were going to die, Sharon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "At one point, yes, I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Sharon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "CD", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "When you reach that kind of abyss in your life, what's the reality about what goes through your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "Well, the one thing that you don't get is, as they're giving you a blood transfusion, I wish I had spent more time at work.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "What were you thinking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "Well, basically I just was looking at my mom and I realized that she wasn't really responsive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "When that happens, it's potentially fatal blow, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "It was one of the craziest things that I've ever seen in my life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "WP", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "And what was it like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "It's very weird what happens because when you're badly injured, you get this adrenaline rush.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "This is back in England, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "And suddenly it was glamour puss Kelly, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "And definitely this show changed me in so many ways.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kelly"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "ORGAN: But if you're honest, when you look at magazines of other women with big asses on the beaches, I mean do you have a little laugh to yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "You don't enjoy the gossip?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "No, I don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "POS", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "Are your lives not perfect, see there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "VB", ",", "VB", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "No one's is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "How much of what I'm looking at is aux natural and how much has been crafted?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "VBZ", "NN", "JJ", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "You know, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 559, "question": "When you see that, what do you think, the changing face of Sharon Osbourne?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 560, "answer": "It was worth the money and made me feel good as a woman.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Sharon Osbourne"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 582, "question": "You are have a very glamorous woman for your age, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 583, "answer": "I think I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "Out of being glamorous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CBS"]}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "``", "DT", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 606, "question": "What did you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "That's you on your show, the CBS show \"The Talk.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "It's really inappropriate thing to say.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 641, "question": "ORGAN: What do you make of Charlie Sheen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 642, "answer": "I think it's sad.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", ":", "CC", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 656, "question": "What do you think it is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 657, "answer": "I think that he definitely suffers from some form of mania, because -- or -- I hate to use the word mental illness, but I don't think -- I think he's a very smart man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 663, "question": "Is that a template for what Charlie could do if he sorts his life out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 664, "answer": "He has got to want it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 673, "question": "What was it for you in the end that stopped you continuing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 674, "answer": "That I wanted to die.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 719, "question": "What have I got on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 720, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 722, "question": "This was ten years ago?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 723, "answer": "The breast look good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 737, "question": "Well, that's half the thing, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 738, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 747, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 748, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 767, "question": "You like her, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 768, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 772, "question": "Did you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 773, "answer": "I did so much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 805, "question": "ORGAN: Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 806, "answer": "Very, very beautiful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 809, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 810, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 811, "question": "Well brought up, you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 812, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 814, "question": "I've got to ask you this, how is your love life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 815, "answer": "I don't have one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 816, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 817, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 820, "question": "Wouldn't you if you were me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 821, "answer": "Pretty bad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 823, "question": "Wouldn't you if you were me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 824, "answer": "I met the infamous ex over that dinner that time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 826, "question": "And it hurt you very much, didn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 827, "answer": "Well, it hurts to get cheated on anyway.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 829, "question": "That's not a good day, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 830, "answer": "Couldn't get worse.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 835, "question": "Did I?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 836, "answer": "Is that why it hurt so much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 844, "question": "Were you ever convinced that he was the guy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 845, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 872, "question": "No?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "aSentId": 873, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 879, "question": "What's that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 880, "answer": "Tweets and Twitter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 886, "question": "What's going on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 887, "answer": "I have no idea.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 921, "question": "You have more than me, you see?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 922, "answer": "I know I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 944, "question": "So many people are boring on Twitter, aren't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 945, "answer": "Oh, yeah, this is me at the dentist.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]